Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for the people in the name of Jesus.
Yes, only Jesus can set us free from addiction and affliction.
Let us see how it's done.
My name is Precious Benyi from Ghana.
I am into drinking and smoking. I can't deal without it.
And sometimes men would pick me, they would give me money and have fun with me.
Man of God, please help me.
When I sleep, I have spiritual marriage. Help me. I am a prostitute.
I am a drunkard. Man of God, please help me. My name is Precious, I'm from Ghana.
Man of God please help me. I am into drinking and smoking.
Man of God, please help me. I can't live without drinking.
For 13 years. I was 15 years, when I got into this.
One day a man asked me for an apple, I gave him an apple.
- You drink this all the time?
- Yes, sir.
- You are addicted to it?
You want to drink it?
In the house of God!
Collect it from her.
You have been drinking it and smoking for how many years?
- Don't smoke here.
- 13 years.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Devil. Come on. It's devil.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Leave her alone. She doesn't belong to you. She is mine.
I want to destroy her. I want to destroy her life.
She dupes people, she seduces men, after that she runs away.
Yes, I don't want her to progress.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
My name is Precious. I was addicted to smoking and drinking.
I was an international prostitute.
I started it, when I was 15 years.
It all started like this: one day on my way going to an examination for our mock, JSS mock,
I met this man, I was eating apple. And this man told me to give him one of my apples.
So when I gave him the one I had not eaten, he said
I should give me the one I had already eaten. So I gave him the one I had already eaten.
And when he left, he was just smiling.
The next thing I saw in my dreams was this man making love with me.
And when I woke up, I saw myself full of blood on the bed.
I tried to explain it to my mum. My mum was telling me it was my first time, every woman goes through this,
when she want to see her menstruation. She didn't take it seriously.
The next day, I saw myself with these friends - I was with them in school.
I wasn't spending time with them before, I didn't even go out with them.
But after this, I saw myself with them.
They came home with me. They said they want us to go to school together.
And they didn't even take me to school. We first went to a house.
One of the girls said the headmaster rented the house for her.
So they took me into the room and I asked: "What about the exams?"
She said we shouldn't bother about the exams because her boyfriend would bring it for us,
including the answers.
I was with them, they now brought out smoke, they soaked it with alcohol.
And they brought out weed, joints, cigarettes - a lot of cigarettes.
They were all smoking, they were enjoying. They forced me into it.
It wasn't easy for me to taste it, but they forced me.
I didn't smoke much but the drink I drank took over me.
First thing I saw was that I was naked on the bed.
I found out that someone had slept with me.
So I asked her: "What happened to me?"
She didn't say anything. All she was saying was that it was my first time,
and she was going to buy me drugs and I would be fine.
I didn't go home because I wasn't feeling fine and I didn't want my mum to worry.
I still kept on staying with her for the next three days.
I was drinking and smoking with them.
The next three days - we were first at the central part of my country -
we were on the way to the city and I asked about this new face in the car.
We were six girls. The new face that I saw was a very big madam.
I saw her and I asked: "Who is this woman?"
She said the woman was taking us for shopping.
But when she took us to the city, she took us to a guest house.
The next day she took us for shopping.
All the dresses she was buying for us were indecent dresses.
So the next day she took us to one man, it was a herbalist.
It's one of these native doctors, and he is a very powerful man.
The man told us to shave our private parts.
The man prepared a cream for me with my private hair that I had shaved.
The man told me that the cream was going to make me seduce men.
The man told me, the more I would drink and smoke, the more clients I would get.
I should stay away from food.
So I shouldn't eat, I should only eat meat and even if I ate meat,
it should not be cooked by a woman but a man so that I could be getting more clients.
Whenever they called me, I should use the cream on my body.
And what I would do was that I would be mostly drinking
and I would make sure I would finish one bottle in just 30 minutes.
Because when I took the bottle, I didn't drink just beer.
I would drink a strong drink, either red label, whiskey or tequila and I didn't drink in glasses.
I would just pick up the drink and put it in my mouth.
The first one I would take - I had to drink to the half level.
That was the first step. I would take it just three times.
After the second level, I had to finish it to the last level.
And the last level was when the bottle was empty.
After that I could talk to the man.
As I was drinking, the man was getting drunk but not me.
He would look at me and would be confused; whatever I told him, he would be confused.
I would tell him to go and refresh himself - even if he won't go,
he would be there; I would drape his drink, he would not even see it.
Once he took it, he would be confused.
Wherever their money was and what their plans were, they would just tell me:
"This is what I am doing, I am even building a house. I have this money here,
I wanted to deposit it at the meeting tomorrow. They sent me this money."
He could give me the money and ask me whether he should give me all or I should take some of it.
He would even tell me to take all and keep it in my house.
And if he needed some, he would come to me and take it.
What made them to begin to say all these things?
Because I was having this chain.
I would just place it on my neck and make sure I would wear a dark dress
but it should be sexy; I wouldn't just wear anything decent.
When I went out, I would make sure the chain would be in the middle of my breast, to my heart side.
Immediately you set your eye on me, you would just follow me and you would be confused.
If you look closer at it, it's not Jesus on it.
That is our spirit.
- That is your emblem in your kingdom?
- Yes.
So you mean what you are holding now is different from the cross Christians do put on?
Yes, if you look closer at it, you will see that it's not a cross.
So what is the function of this?
The function of it is to negotiate men.
I went back to the native doctor saying I was getting everything I needed but my cream got finished.
So he told me he wanted to make me more powerful and this time, I was going to target pastors.
So he collected my necklace, bracelet and put it on his shrine for just two days.
So he did a cream for me and he told me that
when I went to a church, I should make sure I didn't talk to anybody.
I should put the cream in my mouth
and put it on my face and the first person I should talk to
was the usher - before I would get to the church.
And I should make sure I would sit in the front so that the pastor was going to locate me.
I could go anytime I wanted.
Immediately I got to the church, I would tell the usher, I wanted to sit in the front.
No matter who was sitting at the front seat, she would go and remove the person and put me there
or he would go and remove the person and put me there.
And I would sit in the front. As soon as the pastor would see me - even if he was praying
or preaching - he would just concentrate on me.
Highest was 15 minutes - he would call me out.
He would just bring out a paper and a pen: "This is a quotation I want to give to you.
Then you should go through it, when you go home. This is between you and your God."
He would just write his number and tell you: "Make sure your number will come on my phone."
So I would make sure my number was going to go to his phone before I would leave the church.
Immediately he would see me leaving the church, he would leave the church
and follow me wherever I was going.
Even when the service was still going on?
Yes, even when the service was going on. I had already negotiated him.
So what would happen is that, that same day, whether he was married or he was not married,
he had to sleep with me. I negotiated them, giving them sickness
which would then put them into disgrace.
Some would be sleeping with animals. Some would be sleeping with their own children
but they didn't know because I had already negotiated them.
So the ring was for me to be disappearing.
If I disappeared and I went to a place where there was a leaf, I should just tie myself on the leaf
and I would see myself on my bed in my house.
So that was what I was doing. I got myself into a trouble one day.
I found myself getting to a place where there were no leaves.
I saw this woman coming out from mass and she removed her head tie to cover me.
It was a very big head scarf.
When you are naked and you get to somewhere in my country, they will think you are a bird, a witch,
They will kill you or they will send you to newspapers.
But whenever I got into this trouble, I would get into the hands of God's people
that would cover me and even advise me to take me out of it.
Because of the pastors I tempted and I broke a lot of homes,
a lot of people were praying against whoever was the cause of it, I was frustrated.
My master wasn't working for me anymore.
I even got attacked to remove the ring on my finger because I started seeing these short
native doctor's things; they would be dancing around me, playing drums.
Sometimes I would be confused.
Wherever I was, I acted like a mad person.
The man told me that nobody would help me and I should make sure
I would not throw this chain away because if I threw it away, I was going to be mad.
They prepared it personally for me.
Nobody was going to help me or even take all those things away for me.
But I shouldn't step my feet there again or he himself would strike me with madness.
When I was walking on the way, I saw this man - he asked me for money.
That was the last money because I didn't eat food. I would only drink and smoke.
This man said: "You're going to buy cigarettes with this money.
Give me the money and God will bless you."
I just gave him the money and he told me: "Don't bother about the money you have given me.
God has forgiven you all your sins. It wasn't you but you were negotiated.
So run to The Synagogue, Church Of All Nations for your deliverance."
I just saw the man as a mad person. I left there.
After that I was not myself until I started seeing the man in my dream.
He was still telling me that I should come and see my daddy in the Lord to deliver me.
That was what brought me to The Synagogue, Church Of All Nations for my deliverance.
Precious
Deliverance Testimony
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Precious Benyi, I am from Ghana.
The problem that brought me to The Synagogue, Church Of All Nations was that I was addicted
to drinking and smoking and prostitution.
And today I'm here to testify to the glory of God.
I was delivered three years ago.
God has really done a lot in my life.
I'm really grateful.
I was a prostitute, yes, and not just the cheap one on the street.
This one was executive prostitute - on ministers and big man in my country.
Today I'm very ashamed of my past.
And I will disgrace the devil today because he couldn't destroy me.
Precious
Deliverance Testimony
I was a prostitute for 15 years. I was out of school when I was just in JSS2.
And this problem really destroyed me a lot in some ways because I was a problem
to my family, a disgrace to my mum and my dad.
They were even ashamed to say: "We know her, she is our family member."
But today, to the glory of God they come to me for advice.
They come to me for help. All because of the grace.
People of God, anyone watching me now in the whole world, I will tell you -
do not be ashamed to let the devil out.
My life before was very terrible. I moved from houses to houses.
A lot of women lost their husbands all because of the evil spirit in me called prostitution.
No matter who you were - if you came into my life, you would never go back to your wife.
I destroyed homes, I spoiled marriages.
I spoiled people's children. I trained girls to be prostitutes.
I gave girls to men. Moving from one house to another.
It was very terrible.
On the 6th of February 2014, I dreamt.
In the dream, men were harassing me.
And it was like I was tired, I was weak in the dream.
I just saw a man coming to me.
"Don't you know that she is my daughter, why are you harassing her?
This is just a daughter of God the demon wants to destroy."
At that time I didn't even know what Emmanuel TV was, who the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua was.
I had never seen him before. What is called man of God? I didn't even know anyone called man of God.
I saw him in my dream that 6th.
And the next year on February 6th, the same date,
I saw a woman with a sticker on the car.
She is close to our family, like a family friend.
When she saw me, I didn't even mind her. I was just standing there talking to someone,
my client who had come to pick me up in the night; we were going out.
When the woman just saw me, she said: "You, come here.
Every day you are doing all these things. Look at what you are doing.
Look at how you are standing outside. You don't even look nice. Why?
Can't you follow me to church? I'm going to church next week."
I said: "What is church?"
"I am going to see the man of God, T.B. Joshua.
I was praying with him on Emmanuel TV to travel out to America.
Now the visa is on. So I'm going for testimony because I'm travelling.
So can you come with me so that you can be delivered?"
I said: "What is called deliverance? Have I told you that I'm possessed?"
I gave it to her very well on the street. She was even disgraced of herself.
But after she left, I heard a voice saying:
"Are you not the one I saw in the dream?
In the harrassment, I saved your life and today you have turned your back on me."
I just realized myself that moment.
So I called aunt Mabel and said: "Aunt Mabel, please come back."
She said: "What is it? You have insulted me and disgraced me."
I said: "Please, I'm sorry. Who is that man on your sticker I saw on your car?
She said: "He is a man of God, the one I mentioned."
I said, "I have seen him in my dreams before".
So she now came back to me.
That was why I was introduced and I even remembered
that I had seen the man of God in my dream.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus.
Precious
Deliverance Testimony
On that fateful day I set foot in Nigeria, I said to myself: "God, You know why I am here.
I did not come here on my own but I came here through Your Spirit.
If truly You are God, deliver me out of this drinking and smoking."
To tell you the fact, the hotel I was living in - they couldn't take hold of me,
because I drank and smoked.
They would come to clean the next morning and see cigarettes.
I would be hiding it but the man working there who is a member here
said: "You, I used to see you. Is there anything you are not saying?
Because that church, if you don't say the truth, you can never be fulfilled for your deliverance.
You have to bring out all the truth so that the man of God can deliver you."
He was pampering me for me to say the truth for three days.
I then came and said: "Oga, it's true. I'm a bad girl. I came here for deliverance.
I drink, I smoke, I am a prostitute. As I'm here, I always go down there waiting for the boys to smoke.
And I can't even go to the.. Before I know it, the church time has passed.
That's why I am spending time here. I can't even enter the church."
The next Sunday he forced me to come here.
And later, on the 7th of March, the man of God delivered me; something came out of me.
Like something heavy - boom! Just like that.
I was like empty. If I was walking, I would be thinking I would fall
but it's like something heavy has gotten out of me.
I can sleep well.
Even if I sense a cigarette scent, it seems as if I want to vomit
or I want to just find somewhere where I can breathe.
I can't even breathe out.
Hallelujah!
And I became light, very light.
I used to ask myself: "Do I have weight?"
Because I was very light that time, like a paper.
I am walking freely. I am moving freely like I am empty, like I am free.
Happy all the time.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Precious
Deliverance Testimony
After my deliverance, I had my testimony on the following Sunday,
and I was blessed with money from the man of God.
With the blessing, I did not just make use, like I did not just waste it,
because he is a man of God; I have to make him proud.
I did not use all the money. I did not change all to cedis. I left some behind.
I was using it for a business. I asked God: "What should I use this money for?"
And God revealed to me: "Go into clothing".
So I was travelling from one country to another,
bringing a lot of goods to sell, supplying some people for their shops.
That work I was doing, brought a lot of luck to me and blessing to my family.
I have been able to rent one of the biggest estates in Ghana
and I'm living as a big girl in one of the estates.
Through that work, I have been introduced as a boss -
assistant manager of Shapet Printing in Ghana.
Precious
Deliverance Testimony
The advice I have for people out there listening to me right now is:
You know, when God wants to bless you, He will test your faith.
Before I could be able to stand here for a testimony,
I have really passed through [a lot].
So if you are a child of God, your faith will be tested.
That doesn't mean God is not by your side.
The living God is always by your side.
Now today I am disgraced of my past because now I see myself as a new creature,
as a new beginning of life.
I am blessed, lifted. Everywhere I go, favour is favouring me.
I have never regretted my deliverance and being a Christian.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for Jesus Christ.
Precious
Deliverance Testimony
TT: Monica Asefa 04/12/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 29/12/2018 + Mel